FROM ME TO YOU
I entered middle school
when I was around twelve.
But then in my third year Kitahoro High,
near my house, was holding entrance exams...
At fifteen, in spring...
I met you.
I thought, "If I could become like
Kazehaya... maybe... that could help me grow
and change?"
Thanks a lot!
It was always Kazehaya
who inspired change in me.
This year was so different from all of the
years before... But that part of the story
would take too long.
NEW YEAR
I'm sorry. You must find this so boring.
I do want people to see me in a
better light next year. So I'll try to-
They already do. I'm certain.
It's easier to talk to you now. A lot.
You'll be just fine.
If... If you say something like that... all
the makeup that Ayane just put on me is
gonna...
- I'm sorry!
- Please, just give me three seconds!
Three?
To be honest, I had a good
impression of you to begin with.
You were smiling. Right
before our first day.
It was when you showed
me the way to class.
We were put in the same class.
But I never saw you smile like that again.
So I was curious what
kind of a person you were.
When we met each other for the first
time... I didn't think he remembered that.
I figured you were a nice person, at the
very least... but you turned out to be way
more...
"Way more"?
Wait, so does that mean he
really thinks I'm a nice person?
Even today, I was surprised
because you were so different.
What?! I apologize! Scaring you
like that was never my intention!
Ugh, that's not what I meant by that...
It's not.
Huh? Then what?
Forget it! Let's line up at the shrine.
It's almost time!
They already do. I'm certain.
If you say that I'm
changing, then it might be true...
Remember when you first met Kurumi, you
mentioned how you wanted to become cuter?
You have a reason for wanting that
don't you? Think about what it is.
Ayane, after thinking about
it, there's only one answer.
My feelings are all over the place.
I never could have
imagined... you'd be this cute.
Before, I just wanted to
become more like Kazehaya...
But now, all I care about is how to
make him think I'm as cute as possible.
Touching...
- What is this? And when is it gonna end?
- Dunno. When Joe's
tired of Yano-chin I guess?
Seriously, I'm outta here.
Bye, Joe. I'll see ya.
Later, man!
Amazake...
Hold on, Ryu!
Oh. Joe, your jacket...
Nice huh?! I just picked it
up the other day, y'know! Hah!
I think all those holes you got in it
are from getting hit by bonfire sparks.
What?
- Bye now...
- But what about
praying pray at the shrine!
- And after we came all the way out here...
- Chizu, just go.
Huh?
You probably didn't explain anything to
him and just dragged him along, right? Go
on! Get outta here!
I'm sorry, Yano-chin! The
ramen's on me next time!
Nah, that's okay. I'll get fat.
It was expensive too...
But, now we're alone.
Ryu! Hey, hold up! How
come you ran off like that?
Sorry. It was too dumb I
couldn't stand it anymore.
That was blunt. Would it kill
you to try being a little nicer?
Yeah! Try to say
"Chii" for me, 'kay? Chii!
Absolutely not.
How come? It'll make you smile.
Well, either way...
No matter how Kuronuma acts or who they
end up running into, Shota's got it under
- control.
- W-Well, yeah! I guess that's true.
Jus' leave 'em alone.
You're being too nosy.
We just wanted to sneak a peek at 'em.
Besides, I don't think that there's
anything to worry about. At least it seems
like it's going well.
See?
So yeah, I'm gonna have
some amazake and leave.
No. You're not. You are gonna
come pray at the shrine with me.
Wha-- Amazake...
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One! Happy New Year!
- And a Happy New Year to you!
- And a Happy New Year to
you! I'm lookin' forward to it.
Y-Yeah, same here! I'm looking
forward to the next one too!
Another year!
Text?
Huh?
Oh yeah, I do have one! There's two!
They're from Chizu and Ayane!
Are you gonna reply?
Wait, can I?!
Of course!
Ha... ppy... New... Year... There...
Even with texting her you
beat me to the punch. Oh, well.
Because of you, I'm
having fun. So, thanks.
Ah, Sawako sent me a text back!
And it looks like she
returned my "Happy New Year."
"I'm looking forward to
spending another year with you."
Last year, I experienced so
many things for the first time.
You ready? It's our turn.
HOW TO PRAY:
TWO BOWS
And the reason I was able to experience...
and even enjoy all of these new things...
Was because I met everyone.
It was a truly
unforgettable year for me. Thank you.
- Woo, be careful. It's slippery.
- Y... you're right.
Here.
My brother said he'll
be back New Year's Day...
With her.
You, uh... haven't
memorized her name yet, have you?
She got me.
It's Haruka! Get it together, man!
She's gonna be your sister-in-law, right?
But, I'll be there.
Ryu.
If anything ever happens to you, ya know?
I'm gonna be there to help you pick up all
the pieces, okay?
If it ever does, I'll count on you.
- Let's draw fortunes.
- Sure.
FORTUNES
100 YEN
- I got Great Luck!
- Amazing!
"Everything will go your way."
"Suppress your impatience and behave
yourself, always maintain a calm state of
mind." "Be sure to seek out advice
from others..." Can I do all this?
I- I wonder what I ended up with.
Hmmm, maybe Small
Luck? I doubt I got Great...
I should've lowered my expectations.
I feel like I've started
getting a little too greedy lately...
Alright then? What'd you get?
Umm,... well...
LOVE: THE CURRENT PERSON IS BEST,
DO NOT QUESTION IT.
Oh, Bad Luck.
The best...
- That couldn't be more true.
- It's actually lucky! I
mean it. 'Cuz it's rare!
What? Really?
You usually tie these onto
the tree branches, right?
Kuronuma.
Here. I want you to have this.
Your Great Luck fortune?
But that's how do I put it...
I feel like I might steal all the
luck from you if I accept your fortune...
It's fine, take it.
I already have good luck. Besides...
I mean...
I want to give it to you...
Though for a birthday
gift it might be kinda lame.
Th-Thank you.
Have I ever really questioned it?
Thinking back on it, how could I not tell
these feelings were something romantic the
whole time? It doesn't make sense.
I don't know... how I ever saw him
as only someone to be admired.
Awesome! I spent the New
Year's countdown alone with Ayane!
I finally found you! This kid! I swear!
You promised me that you'd stay close to
the bonfire 'mister!
Gosh, sorry for all the trouble.
Thanks for looking after our stupid son.
Mom, wait, I'm in the middle of
something very important right now!
Uh, no prob.
Come on, we're going home! -Ayane! -Look
at all these holes! No New Year's money
for you! -What, no! That's not fair, Mom!
I've been saved...
Dear God, please completely erase the
fact that I was with Joe on New Year's.
Wipe it from everyone's memory,
especially mine. That's all I ask of you.
Well! Looks like those two
are getting along just fine.
Then... guess I'll skip pulling my fortune.
But seriously... when they're together like
that, anyone would think
they're a normal happy couple.
Hey, it'll be fun!
You don't know when to
quit. I already told you no!
I don't get it, why not? It's
just getting a little drink!
Sure are a lot of idiots around here.
If Toru were here right now, he could've
talked her into going with us right away,
no problem. That jerk. Leavin' me high
and dry to spend New Year's Eve with his
fiancé.
- Marriage, my butt!
- Don't make eye contact, 'kay?
Hey, girly! You goin' solo out here?
We finally meet!
So, you are really cute, you know that?
But you probably hear that a lot, huh?
- I'm falling in love!
- Huh?
- That ain't fair!
- So you should give us your deets!
Random question: how do you
feel about guys with glasses?
- Huh?
That ain't happening!
- See ya!
- Maybe we can go on a
date in your next life...
Thanks for-
The heck are you doing getting
hit on out here, you little goober?!
That means that idiot
back there- was you?
- What's going on?
- What are you following me for?!
A lover's quarrel?
I don't want anything to do with a
kid! How annoying! Don't fall for me!
Don't you worry, you're one
hundred percent safe! I'm going home!
Well, I'm going home too!
You're embarrassing me! Get away will ya?!
CORN SOUP
Once we climb up this hill...
It's our usual path to school.
And also...
This is the place where I
met you for the first time.
It is.
I wonder... what kind of
year lies ahead of us?
So good...
Mhm. Super.
Look, Over there. see
that abandoned house?
Hm? Yeah.
They say there's
something lurking in there.
- Like what?!
- Never mind...
Hey, Tell me! The hell's in
there?! Hey! Don't leave me here!
KITAHORO SHRINE
What about you
Kurumi! What was your wish?
- Tell us, what'd you wish for?
- It's a secret!
- Aww, how come? You can tell me!
- Come on, just give us a little peek?
Alright. One peek.
JINGISUKAN FLAVOR
POTATO SNACK
This one?
- Baked chips?
- Yeah! Sure!
Guess we're decided then!
- Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year! So
- what are you guys up to?
- Waiting for the countdown!
Yeah!
- We're doin' that too!
Hey! Here's an idea,
let's enjoy it together then!
You're not hiding your
intentions from anyone.
- It's so late and she's still not back...
- Honey, you really need to relax.
Here try these. Nice and sweet. "Aah."
Ahh...
Oh, it is sweet.
I told you. Have some more.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
See you soon. Okay?
Thanks, Kazehaya.
Tonight was fun! So fun!
It sure was!
- Good night.
- B-Bye. Take care, then!
How long can I suppress
this feeling? This impatience?
I can't take much more.
"Love fortune. Commit to your
love, and happiness will come."
He's a classmate... a boy who
ended up sitting next to me.
But, I... I don't think he can be
considered my friend anymore.
It feels different. He's
more distant than that.
And that only makes me
feel greedy for more...
Because... I love him...